{
    "tileTypes": [
        {
            "uid": 103,
            "name": "sink-right-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "sink-right",
            "back": "sink-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 129,
                "g": 61,
                "b": 156
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 137,
            "name": "sink-right-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "sink-right",
            "back": "sink-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 129,
                "g": 61,
                "b": 156
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 187,
            "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "wire-horizontal",
            "back": "wire-horizontal",
            "color": {
                "r": 192,
                "g": 28,
                "b": 40
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 237,
            "name": "wire-horizontal-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "wire-horizontal",
            "back": "wire-horizontal",
            "color": {
                "r": 4,
                "g": 158,
                "b": 244
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 260,
            "name": "clock-right-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "1",
            "back": "0",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 262,
            "name": "clock-right-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "0",
            "back": "1",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 264,
            "name": "clock-standalone-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "1",
            "back": "0",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 285,
            "name": "clock-standalone-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "0",
            "back": "1",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 317,
            "name": "NOT-right-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "NOT-right",
            "back": "NOT-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 38,
                "g": 162,
                "b": 105
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 351,
            "name": "NOT-right-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "NOT-right",
            "back": "NOT-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 38,
                "g": 162,
                "b": 105
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 426,
            "name": "AND-right-00",
            "up": "0",
            "down": "0",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "AND-right",
            "back": "AND-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 198,
                "g": 70,
                "b": 0
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 447,
            "name": "AND-right-01",
            "up": "0",
            "down": "1",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "AND-right",
            "back": "AND-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 198,
                "g": 70,
                "b": 0
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 468,
            "name": "AND-right-10",
            "up": "1",
            "down": "0",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "AND-right",
            "back": "AND-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 198,
                "g": 70,
                "b": 0
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 489,
            "name": "AND-right-11",
            "up": "1",
            "down": "1",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "AND-right",
            "back": "AND-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 198,
                "g": 70,
                "b": 0
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 658,
            "name": "wire-bend-right-down-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "1",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "wire-bend-right-down",
            "back": "wire-bend-right-down",
            "color": {
                "r": 4,
                "g": 158,
                "b": 244
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 721,
            "name": "wire-bend-right-up-0",
            "up": "0",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "wire-bend-right-up",
            "back": "wire-bend-right-up",
            "color": {
                "r": 192,
                "g": 28,
                "b": 40
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 759,
            "name": "wire-bend-right-up-1",
            "up": "1",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "wire-bend-right-up",
            "back": "wire-bend-right-up",
            "color": {
                "r": 4,
                "g": 158,
                "b": 244
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 1051,
            "name": "clock-right-half-2",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "clock-right-half-2",
            "back": "clock-right-half-1",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 1053,
            "name": "clock-right-half-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "clock-right-half-0",
            "back": "clock-right-half-3",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 1055,
            "name": "clock-right-half-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "clock-right-half-1",
            "back": "clock-right-half-0",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 1057,
            "name": "clock-right-half-3",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "clock-right-half-3",
            "back": "clock-right-half-2",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 1067,
            "name": "wire-bend-right-down-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "0",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "wire-bend-right-down",
            "back": "wire-bend-right-down",
            "color": {
                "r": 192,
                "g": 28,
                "b": 40
            }
        }
    ],
    "savedSubPlaneTilings": [],
    "mainPlaneTiling": {
        "tiles": [
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 260,
                    "name": "clock-right-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "anything",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "1",
                    "back": "0",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 100,
                        "g": 100,
                        "b": 100
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": -2,
                    "y": 2
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 1053,
                    "name": "clock-right-half-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "anything",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "clock-right-half-0",
                    "back": "clock-right-half-3",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 100,
                        "g": 100,
                        "b": 100
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": -2,
                    "y": 0
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 187,
                    "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "wire-horizontal",
                    "back": "wire-horizontal",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": -1,
                    "y": 2
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 187,
                    "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "wire-horizontal",
                    "back": "wire-horizontal",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 0,
                    "y": 2
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 187,
                    "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "wire-horizontal",
                    "back": "wire-horizontal",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": -1,
                    "y": 0
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 187,
                    "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "wire-horizontal",
                    "back": "wire-horizontal",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 0,
                    "y": 0
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 1067,
                    "name": "wire-bend-right-down-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "0",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "anything",
                    "front": "wire-bend-right-down",
                    "back": "wire-bend-right-down",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 1,
                    "y": 2
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 721,
                    "name": "wire-bend-right-up-0",
                    "up": "0",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "anything",
                    "front": "wire-bend-right-up",
                    "back": "wire-bend-right-up",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 1,
                    "y": 0
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 426,
                    "name": "AND-right-00",
                    "up": "0",
                    "down": "0",
                    "left": "anything",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "AND-right",
                    "back": "AND-right",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 198,
                        "g": 70,
                        "b": 0
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 1,
                    "y": 1
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 187,
                    "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "wire-horizontal",
                    "back": "wire-horizontal",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 2,
                    "y": 1
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 187,
                    "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "0",
                    "front": "wire-horizontal",
                    "back": "wire-horizontal",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 192,
                        "g": 28,
                        "b": 40
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 3,
                    "y": 1
                }
            },
            {
                "tileType": {
                    "uid": 103,
                    "name": "sink-right-0",
                    "up": "anything",
                    "down": "anything",
                    "left": "0",
                    "right": "anything",
                    "front": "sink-right",
                    "back": "sink-right",
                    "color": {
                        "r": 129,
                        "g": 61,
                        "b": 156
                    }
                },
                "r": {
                    "x": 4,
                    "y": 1
                }
            }
        ],
        "name": ""
    },
    "cachedPlaneTiling": {
        "tiles": [],
        "name": ""
    },
    "colorMap": {
        "0": {
            "r": 192,
            "g": 28,
            "b": 40
        },
        "1": {
            "r": 4,
            "g": 158,
            "b": 244
        },
        "ANYTHING": {
            "r": 0,
            "g": 0,
            "b": 0
        },
        "sink-right": {
            "r": 129,
            "g": 61,
            "b": 156
        },
        "wire-horizontal": {
            "r": 61,
            "g": 56,
            "b": 70
        },
        "NOT-right": {
            "r": 143,
            "g": 240,
            "b": 164
        },
        "AND-right": {
            "r": 255,
            "g": 190,
            "b": 111
        },
        "new-tile-0": {
            "r": 36,
            "g": 31,
            "b": 49
        },
        "wire-bend-right": {
            "r": 36,
            "g": 31,
            "b": 49
        },
        "wire-bend-right-down": {
            "r": 36,
            "g": 31,
            "b": 49
        },
        "wire-bend-right-up": {
            "r": 36,
            "g": 31,
            "b": 49
        },
        "clock-right-half-0": {
            "r": 4,
            "g": 158,
            "b": 244
        },
        "clock-right-half-1": {
            "r": 4,
            "g": 158,
            "b": 244
        },
        "clock-right-half-2": {
            "r": 192,
            "g": 28,
            "b": 40
        }
    }
}